antivirustop10.com 2019-01-14

# Antivirus Best 10 - Privacy Policy 2016

**WE ARE COMMITTED TO SAFEGUARDING THE PRIVACY OF OUR WEBSITE VISITORS. THIS POLICY SETS OUT HOW WE WILL TREAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.**

**1\. Personal Data**   
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:   
1.1 information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);   
1.2 information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;   
1.3 information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including name, address, telephone number and financial information);   
1.4 information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters);   
p.1.5 any other information that you choose to send to us; and   
1.6 any other information. 

**2\. Cookies**   
2.1 A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.   
2.2 We may use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to enable our website to recognise you when you visit. 

**3\. Using your personal data**   
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. 

We may use your personal information to:   
3.1 administer the website;   
3.2 improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;   
3.3 enable your use of the services available on the website;   
3.4 send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;   
3.5 send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;   
3.6 send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;   
3.7 send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;   
3.8 send to you marketing communications relating to our business and specifically Packaged Bank Account Claims or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);   
3.9 provide third parties with statistical information about our users;   
3.10 deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and   
3.11 contact you via text message, email or by post. 

**4\. Disclosures**   
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.   
In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

4.1 to the extent that we are required to do so by law; 4.2 in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; and 4.3 in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). 

**5\. International data transfers**   
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.   
Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States and other countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas (EEA)).   
You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information. 

**6\. Security of your personal data**   
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. 

**7\. Policy amendments**   
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

**8\. Your rights**   
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).   
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.) 

**9\. Third party websites**   
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. 

**10\. Updating information**   
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. 

**11\. Contact**   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email at support@antivirustop10.com or by post to Twenty One Marketing Limited Company at 85 Great Portland Street, First Floor, London, W1W 7LT 

**12\. Data controller**   
The data controller responsible for our website is Twenty One Marketing Limited Company at 85 Great Portland Street, First Floor, London, W1W 7LT
